<Document>
# Contraband

  Contraband are dangerous items which could put you at odds with CGP. Might be best to understand what can get you in hot water.

##  Understanding Contraband

  First you want to examine an item with either right click or shift+click to examine something.
  After that look at the bottom there should be a RED lock button you hover over that lock with a mouse it will show the contraband level.

## Crime And Contraband

  When you commit crime any dangerous items could be confiscated and could even be taken away by CGP.
  To top it all off you could get sentenced with both Possession and Brandishing.
  So keep your wit about you and hide your stash.

 ## Levels Of Contraband You Might See

  [color=red]This item is military grade equipment, and highly restricted.[/color]

  [color=yellow]This item is classified as a destructive device, and is illegal to possess without a permit.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This item is Black Market contraband, and is illegal to possess.[/color]

  [color=red]This item is restricted to CGP and command staff, and is illegal to possess.[/color]

 [color=yellow]This item is considered class 1 contraband, and may be taken from you on committing a crime.[/color]

  [color=red]This item is considered class 2 contraband, civilian possession is illegal without a permit.[/color]

  [color=red]This unregistered weapon is considered class 2 contraband, civilian possession is illegal without a permit.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This unregistered weapon is considered class 3 contraband, civilian possession is illegal.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This cult item is considered class 3 contraband, and its possession is illegal.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This item is considered class 3 contraband, and its possession is illegal.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This pirate item is considered class 3 contraband, and its possession is illegal.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This Syndicate item is considered class 3 contraband, and its possession is illegal.[/color]

  [color=crimson]This Wizard item is considered class 3 contraband, and its possession is illegal.[/color]

  [color=yellow]This item may be a highly valuable target for pirates![/color]

  [color=magenta]This individual is deemed too dangerous to be contained, and is considered as class 3 contraband when in captivity. Keeping them in confinement, alive or dead, is illegal.[/color]

  [color=magenta]This creature is deemed too dangerous to be contained, and is considered as class 3 contraband when in captivity. Keeping it in confinement, alive or dead, is illegal.[/color]

  [color=magenta]This intelligence is deemed too dangerous to be contained, and is considered as class 3 contraband when in captivity. Keeping it in confinement, alive or dead, is illegal.[/color]

</Document>
