<Document>

  # New Frontiers definitions and terms

This section will explain most the common terminology used on the server both in character and out of character.

  ## Panic Bunker
  Server tool that does not let in account with less than 10 hours of gameplay into the server if there is no admin present, one of the most effective tools up to this date to avoid the constant stream of raiders and griefers into the server.

  ## Raider
  Organized group of online people with the intention to break the server rules, ruin your round or just kill your character with no intention to RP, be armed and prepared to defend yourself and contact admins trough Ahelp to report and ban them.

  ## Ahelp
  Short for Admin Help, can be accessed via F1 to directly contact with the server moderation team to report issues, ask for advise or help.

  ## LTAP
  <!-- Wayfarer: removed NFSD replaced with CGP-->
  Leaving To Avoid Punishment refers to leaving the game in the middle of an ahelp inquiry started by the admins, while being forced to read the rules or leaving the server on a constant basis after being arrested by the CGP for commiting a crime. [color=red]Doing this will lead to a ban or make it more severe.[/color]

  ## Levels of chat
  - IC (In Character): All conversation in world and in game, taking into consideration the lore and rp other players are having.
  - OOC (Out Of Character): All conversation with knowledge outside the game and themes that do not take inside the game universe (disabled mid round).
  - LOOC (Local Out Of Character): Same as OOC but spans the range of only your character.

  ## Metacommunications
  The sharing of ingame information trough outside communications like VC(Voice Chat), discord or any other means, be it for the means of cheating the game or to teach someone.

  ## POI
  <!-- Wayfarer: replaced Frontier outpost with Dusk-->
  Acronym for Point Of Interest, it is used for every station that spawns at the start of the round and acts as a meeting point where shuttles can dock at, examples being Tinnia's, Dusk, The Pit, Medical Dispatch and so on.

  ## Safezone
  The area encircling the Frontier Outpost with a span of 200m from the center of the station, completely invulnerable and with a pacification field for anyone under 10 hours of gameplay.

  ## Powergaming
  A display of consistent pattern of antisocial and unsporting behavior in which a player prioritizes their game experience at the expense of others through routine optimization and abuse of game mechanics/knowledge.

  ## Highgrading
  Refers to the act of buying ships, stripping its machinery or cutting out sections to merge it all together into a single vessel with the intention to bypass interacting with other player's ships to obtain resources/tech/food effectively trying to obtain everything on the game alone.

  ## SSD (Sudden Sleep Disease)
  IC term for going AFK or disconnecting from the game, it is considered for them to still be alive and should be roleplayed as any sleeping being.

  ## CGP
  <!-- Wayfarer: removed NFSD replaced with CGP, replace pirates with outlaws-->
  Acronym for the Concordia Galactic Peacekeepers, the policing force of the sector that counters the outlaws and upholds the order.

  ## Space Law
  The system of rules that character have to follow IC depending on their role and affiliation, can be broken with exceptions, for more information consult rules section on [textlink="Crimes" link="FrontierRule10"].

  ## NFZ (No Fly Zone)
  <!-- Wayfarer: removed NFSD replaced with CGP-->
  Term often used by the CGP to impose a restricted imaginary area on space with a determined range from there it is not permitted to go into without a permission.

  ## UIV
  <!-- Wayfarer: removed Nanotrasen replaced with Concordia-->
  Unidentified Vessel, a ship with no designation that is part of either a criminal or more dangerous organization not affiliated with Concordia.

  ## Centcom
  <!-- Wayfarer: removed Nanotrasen replaced with Concordia, change company to colony-->
  Central command is considered the headquarters of Concordia, the colony that invested and has influence over the sector, often usually used to refer to the admins IC by saying "im faxing/messaging centcom".


  other slang terms you might encounter throughout the community !

  # In-Character Slang
  <!-- wayfarer: added over some stuff from Resources/ServerInfo/Guidebook/Glossary.xml for more text mentions, with various edits-->
  These are terms you might encounter in-game.

  ## AOS
  Arrest on sight.

  ## Atmos
  Short for Atmospherics.

  ## Atmosian
  A term for Atmospheric Technicians, or generally anyone who spends most of their time or is particularly skilled with Atmospherics.

  ## Bolted
  An airlock that will never change states. It will stay permanently open or permanently closed until it is unbolted. Closed and bolted airlocks have solid red lights.

  ## Braindead
  Refers to a user who has disconnected from the game. Disconnected users may still reconnect to the server and assume control of their character again.

  ## Brig
  The main area of the security department. This is where prisoners are brought and held for their punishment. The Warden is in charge of the brig's smooth operation.

  ## Cap
  Short for Captain.

  ## CE
  Short for Chief Engineer, the head of the Engineering Department.

  ## CentComm/Central Command
  An administrative agency which oversees the Nanotrasen space station you inhabit.

  ## DOC
  <!-- wayfarer: CMO to DOC-->
  Short for Director of care, the head of the Medical Department.

  ## Crit/Critical
  Refers to the health state at which you fall unconscious and unable to move. While in critical, your health slowly decays until you die, unless you happen to get outside assistance.

  ## Emag
  Refers to the Syndicate cryptographic sequencer. "Emagged" usually refers to airlocks or lockers that are bolted open, but also any other device hacked into by an Emag.

  ## Emergency Access/EA
  An airlock that can be opened by anyone, even without access or an ID at all. Airlocks that are set to emergency access have blinking yellow lights.

  ## ERT
  An Emergency Response Team. These may be dispatched by Central Command for a number of purposes.

  ## God(s)
  An IC term representing a Server Administrator. CentComm is also sometimes used in this manner.

  ## Insuls
  Short for Insulated Gloves. These are the yellow gloves most often worn by Engineers. They are offer complete protection from getting electrocuted from shocked things. Vastily more effective than their budget variety.

  ## Jani
  Short for Janitor.

  ## KOS
  Kill on sight. Someone has commited such a serious crime that they are deemed not even worth arresting.

  ## Mats
  Materials. Usually steel, plastic, plasteel, glass, silver and gold.

  ## Perma
  Short for Permanent Brig. This is for the most serious crime and means that a prisoner will never be released. Most stations have a dedicated, separate area of security for the permanent brig.

  ## QM
  Short for Quartermaster, the head of the Cargo department.

  ## RD
  Short for Research Director, the head of the Science Department.

  ## Robust
  A word used to describe someone who is particularly adept in combat, or endured through a tough fight.

  ## Salv
  Short for Salvage tech.

  ## Sci
  Short for Science.

  ## Sec
  Short for Security.

  ## Secoff
  Short for Security Officer.

  ## Shift
  In-Character way to refer to rounds.

  ## Singulo
  A shortening of the Singularity Engine. A Singulo can create infinite power for the station but is very dangerous.

  ## Singuloose
  A Singularity that has grown too much and breached its containment. It will rip through the station causing massive damage.

  ## Spacing
  An event which causes an area to lose air pressure, i.e. a hull breach.

  ## Spess
  An intentional mis-spelling of "Space", sometimes used as a portmanteau of "space" and "mess". May also appear in words such as "Spessmen".

  ## SSD
  Short for Sudden Sleep Disorder or Space Sleep Disorder. This is an in-character way to refer to a player who has disconnected and is no longer responding.

  ## TC
  A telecrystal, which is a currency used by criminal agents to purchase restricted contraband such as weapons and other illegal equipment.

  ## Xenoarchaeology
  Study of artifacts, usually performed by science.

  # Out-Of-Character Slang

  These are terms you should only be using in OOC chat or outside the game.

  ## Admeme
  An event hosted or caused by an admin. or the admin just pulling prank on you.

  ## AHelp/Admin Help
  A relay used to report rulebreaking behavior or other issues to administrators.

  ## Antag
  Short for Antagonists, which are specifically picked individuals designed to drive the round into chaos.

  ## Bwoink
  The noise made when an admin-help is received. Pray this isn't a ban.

  ## Ick Ock
  A phrase usually shouted in OOC when somebody reveals IC current round information, or "in-character, out-of-character".

  ## LOOC/OOC
  Local out-of-character and (global) out-of-character respectively. They are text channels that allow players to talk to other players outside of roleplay. LOOC is enabled during rounds, while OOC is typically only on after the round ends.

  ## LRP
  Low Roleplay. Servers marked LRP typically have relaxed roleplaying rules.

  ## MRP
  Medium Roleplay. Servers marked MRP usually have a decent basis of roleplaying rules and generally require players to act as their character would realistically in a given situation. Less leeway is afforded to behavior such as openly defying Security or your boss.

  ## HRP
  High Roleplay. Servers marked HRP generally have extensive rules on what is and is not constituted while playing a character. You are generally required to act as your character would, have a character backstory, and follow protocol on the station. Some HRP servers may create their own lore or settings to further facilitate the type of server they wish to host.

  ## Self-Antag
  A term for a player who engages in antagonist-like activity without actually being an antagonist. This encompasses a wide variety of behavior, but is typically used to describe annoying behavior or actions which are greatly detrimental to other players for no purpose. Self-antagonism is a bannable offense. Sometimes used in IC. DO NOT DO THIS.

  ## Upstream
  The baseline version of the game. Any changes to Upstream will "flow" down to all other forks of the game. All official Wizard's Den servers work off of Upstream.

</Document>
