<Document>

  # Smuggling Prevention
  <!-- Wayfarer: NFSD mention remove.-->
  As an officer in the CGP, part of your job is to prevent smuggling.
  <!-- Wayfarer: Syndicate mention remove.-->
  Smugglers use [color=#9ef5ff]dead drops[/color], objects where the criminal agent leaves notes with clues to the location of [color=#c4261d]drop pods[/color] filled with contraband.

  Remember:
  - These are spread across the seedier points of interest across the sector.
  - Use any clue you might find lying around.
  - Ask around to see if the public's seen suspicious activity.
  - Be on the lookout for strange traffic patterns.
  <!-- Wayfarer: NFSD mention remove.-->
  As CGP officers, part of your job is to prevent smuggling, and to catch smugglers in the act.
  <!-- Wayfarer: nanotrasen monopoly remove.-->
  Keep commerce in the sector strong, for a secure future.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateTradeContrabandSecure1" Caption="contraband crate"/>
  </Box>

  ## Notifications

  When a note is taken from a [color=#9ef5ff]dead drop[/color], a [color=#c4261d]drop pod[/color] is teleported into the sector. This [color=#c4261d]drop pod[/color] contains cargo, some of it contraband, and these illicit goods tend to be sold for profit.
  <!-- Wayfarer: nanotrasen mention remove.-->
  With cutting-edge bluespace technology, [bold]we can get signatures when these notes are taken[/bold], and, with some delay, get [bold]the approximate location of a [color=#c4261d]drop pod[/color][/bold].

  Due to the nature of bluespace, [bold]these notifications are not completely reliable[/bold], but that is no excuse for laziness. Remain vigilant.

  ## Forensics

  As an incentive to prevent smuggling and catch active smugglers, a [color=#5d8c45]contraband forensics module[/color] comes standard in a Detective's gear. [bold]Using these rewards your department for good field work[/bold].
  <!-- Wayfarer: NFSD, FUC, and syndicate mention remove.-->
  [color=#5d8c45]Scanning[/color] active or previously used [color=#9ef5ff]dead drops[/color], and Outlaw [color=#c4261d]drop pods[/color] credits the CGP's bank with spesos and ZCs(Zekke Credits). ZCs will be paid out to the scanning officer when enough have been collected.

  [bold]You get bigger rewards by being the first to a [color=#9ef5ff]dead drop[/color], so get moving![/bold]

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ContrabandForensicsModule" Caption="forensics module"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FrontierUplinkCoin"/>
  </Box>
  <!-- Wayfarer: NFSD mention remove.-->
  [bold]Remember to use any DNA you find to track down and prosecute the smugglers.[/bold] It is one of your duties as an CGP officer to keep sector commerce legal.

</Document>
